Hello Hello Friends, I am Amit Malviya, once
again a very warm
welcome to all of you in the new video of our YouTube channel.
So friends, if you are a serial
and you want to do insurance work at your center
like motor third party
insurance or you
want to do nikla insurance, then today's
video is going to be very important for you.
So in today's
video, I am going to tell you how to do
motor third party insurance
and how much
commission will the bailee get for it, what is the process of that company
and from which company is the best
insurance to do, like it is
very easy for SSE to do insurance,
so in today's video you will get complete
information, so do
watch the video without entering it and yes,
I am on the channel, so like every time,
subscribe to the channel and press the alarm
because on our channel you keep getting videos about
similar CSE services, so
let's start today's amazing video.
So friends, for this, first of all I would like you to login to
your digital service portal.  If you want to
take Digital Seva Portal,
after logging in, you have to simply click on Service. As soon as
you select Service, then
many services open in front of you in the pose
as you can see and
you also get the search button here.
So when you type ICICI here,
friends, before this
I have made a complete video for HDFC Agro.
If you want to take this HDFC Agro
insurance policy,
then you
can buy HDFC Agro policy through that video.
You will get the video in the i button. Now
friends, in today's video I am making it about this group in
which you have a very
good benefit that you do
not need to fill any details. That
means if you enter the vehicle number, then the details
of the vehicle are filled there. It is very easy for you to fill in the complete details of the vehicle. That is why
I am
telling you about ICICI. Today's video, if you
simply type ICICI here, then
here it will appear before you as ICICI
and here it will appear
before you as motor.  Third Party Rep, these two
options will appear in front of you, here you will
get the clear button, then you simply have to
click on the new model conference Europe,
so here you will be
asked to log in to Dish Wood, so here you will
enter your user ID here, you will enter the fifth here,
so you will fill it here,
click on the sign in button, then a
page like this opens in front of you,
friends, here you have got to
see the product, here you are
seeing the option 'Back to Two Wheeler', here
you will get to see two-wheeler TV,
so what you have to do is to select '
Two Wheeler TP', so as you click here, you will
reach an interface like this, you have to click on 'Get Quit', then
a form like this will open in front of you,
as you can see, now friends,
what you have to do here, as you can see,
you get an option, it
is highlighted in blue color, 'Get ITO Details', okay, so
here simply you have to enter the vehicle number  This
is the vehicle number, you should check it by entering the audio here first,
so
you have to enter the vehicle number carefully here, so here
we have entered 9.50, after that
you have to click on get audio DJ, so
as you click on best audio details,
whatever information of the vehicle is there
by RTO,
you can see here, it takes a lot of information
here automatically,
after that you have to go here,
if your manufacturer is Hero,
then you will select
Bajaj, TVS here, then you
will click here and there, now as you are seeing ours,
if you get an option to
see, then in one the name is
not there here, hence in other manufacturer it comes
Hero Motor Corp Ltd, so here your
model number is also there, you have got the complete details to
see here,
okay, now what you have to do is simple, you will
get an option to see here, right on the left to take
Hussain, so you should note down this option  If you want to
give it, right? Then
select your button here, after that you will be able to go down,
you can see the update quad here,
you will simply click here,
as you click here, then
here the premium diesel will appear in front of you,
how much third party payment you have to pay, click on the profit button,
as if you click on the profit button, then
here you will
get the complete details, right? Yes, you
can see it here, now if you
want to separate a nominee here, then you
will click here, you can add the nominee details here,
like the name of the nominee
here, nominee's relationship ma'am, after that
here is Dominica age, you can add it here,
after that you will create a
new customer here, which you will do for Airtel,
Mr. or Mrs., whatever it is, and after that,
here you will enter the customer's name, village friends,
here you have to fill the customer's date of birth,
you have to enter the name here,
after that come here and enter the customer's linear
address, you have to enter this surgery,
whatever you have here  You will select the pin code of the area,
after that you will
select the university here, come here and
select the state, okay, here you will have to
enter the email address of the customer, the
policy in one goes to the mail,
sometimes you will have to enter it here
and the monitory is here, you will
enter the mobile number of the customer and
click on generate proposal,
as generated, now when you click on the proposal, the
proposal number will appear in front of you here, okay, you have to
take a screenshot of it, after that now you will
join on the button named buy, as soon as you
click on the buy now button, you will be
directed to your wallet, now
friends, the very good thing here is that
you are seeing that the saver mode of this is
887, which means 883 rupees and
your 898 rupees will be deducted from the wallet, which means you
get commission on the fee here,
this is a very good commission on one policy, you will
enter the password of your CSC ID here,
after that click on the validate button
here, then again you will
enter the wallet password and  Here you will
click on the button, then
like when you click on the first button,
your policy card gets
generated here, here you get the option to download the policy, so as soon as
you click on the download button here, then
your policy which you are seeing here,
this policy starts downloading,
your policy will be downloaded here, you can
take its printout and easily provide it to your customer
and here
you
can earn a very good commission by working under ICICI Lombard, so
friends, in today's video, the complete
process of how to quote third party
insurance, what is its complete process
and how much commission will be received, I have provided you all the complete
information in today's video,
so if you
liked the video, then like and share the video
and yes, if you are not on the channel, then
definitely support your brother by subscribing to the channel,
I will meet you in the next video, till then
Jai Hind 6